Oh, no.
Oh, damn it!
"Get the kids inside!
Let's go!"
Move!
"All right, you know what to do!"
Quickly! Quickly!
"Get 'em inside!"
All right, let's go, men.
This is not a drill.
Take the guns.
Go get your ammo.
That's it.
I'm Special Agent Dennis Abbott
with the FBI.
Means nothing here.
Well, that's okay, son.
I'd like to speak
with whoever's in charge here.
They'll send someone out
if they wanna send someone out.
Easy! Easy.
Guys, does it have to be so serious?
Can we just relax a little?
It's the DOJ again.
Need to get used to it.
Our victim was a high-profile
U.S. attorney.
The solicitor general's
demanding answers.
"Uh, no problemo, Moises."
Uh, they're...
they're with me.
Hey, Jane.
- How was the flight?
- Fine.
- How long you been here?
- Oh, about an hour or so.
Yeah, that thing is very smooth,
very smooth on the freeway.
I told you it'd be faster to drive.
Where's, uh, Lisbon? No Lisbon?
Back in Austin. She's still dealing
with Ardiles' murder.
- Oh, I'm fine.
- No, thanks.
You're missing out.
It's very, very good.
Uh, Commander Delgado
Special Agent Fischer,
Special Agent Cho.
As soon as I heard the victim was
an attorney for the U.S. Government
I made this case my top priority.
This way, please.
So, Commander Delgado, how did you ID
the body so quickly?
Medical alert bracelet.
This is Edith Firlock.
53 years of age, had a severe nut
and dairy allergy.
That's not what killed her.
It was a bullet to the brain.
I've already conducted
my examination.
Thank you, Jane.
- What time was the body found?
- 8:00 this morning.
Lack of blood on-scene suggests
that she was shot somewhere else
and dumped here.
- Any witnesses see the body arrive?
- None that will talk about it.
Clean shot to the back
of the head, execution-style.
Could be Juarez cartel.
The local police are exploring
that angle right now.
I'm telling you guys, the commander
and I have been through all of this.
Let's just save a little time,
shall we?
Have a look at the t-shirt.
The sandals.
And this...
tattoo.
It looks like an insignia.
So, she has a tattoo
and likes casual clothing.
But she doesn't.
She's a federal attorney.
The clear nail polish and the conservative
hairstyle suggest that she...
she worked very hard to look
well-groomed and authoritative...
Yet she's dressed up
as an old-fashioned hippie.
It's a costume.
Undercover.
What is that about?
Firlock lived in Fort Worth. Do we know
why she was in Mexico?
Nah, she had no official business
down here.
Border patrol says Edith Firlock
never crossed into Mexico.
We have no record of her
flying or driving here.
Well, she crossed
the border somehow.
I'll call Wylie, check the surveillance
on our side.
So, lunch.
You like tamales?
Ms. Graham?
Just call me Elsie.
Oh, before I forget...
this was Edith's,
they asked me to bring it.
Thank you.
Please, take a seat.
Edith was always
on that thing.
If she wasn't prepping
for a case, she was photo-sharing.
And how long had you been renting
a room from Edith?
Five years.
We met when she helped me beat
an intent-to-distribute charge.
Never carry a suitcase
across state lines for a man
no matter how good he looks.
Can you think of anybody
in Edith's life
who may have had
a problem with her?
With Edith? No one.
She was the genuine article.
A little gruff,
but she saw the good in people.
Certainly saved my life.
Uh, you're the last person
we can find who saw her
and that was yesterday
at what time?
6:00 a.m.
I was leaving for the early shift
when I ran into her.
Said she'd be back
later that evening.
Now she's dead.
Did she say where she was going?
I didn't ask.
And you're sure she was planning
on coming home last night?
She had a deposition
this morning.
Edith would've never missed that.
Her clients were her life.
If Firlock drove
from Forth Worth to Juarez
she wasn't planning to stay long.
That's a half-day drive each way.
Not to mention the time
she would've spent
- just getting through the border crossing.
- Oh, it's... it's not that bad.
Shorter than airport traffic,
apparently.
I, uh...
I got some lunch.
Tamales de carnitas.
Cho, little napkin, there.
- There we go.
- Thank you.
What if the victim didn't drive
herself to Mexico?
You mean what if she was abducted?
Yeah, that's a possibility.
What do you think, Jane?
Well, I think you're gonna want
some salsa verde with that.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
What do you think
about the case?
Well, she was in costume
pretending to be an old,
leftist hippie.
Uh, you solve that mystery
and I think you'll catch your killer.
If you're right.
Well, it does require paying attention
to some of the details.
Everyone betrays truths
about themselves.
Speaking of which, ah, Cho...
Almost forgot, I got you those
at the marketplace.
- Mexican jumping beans.
- I knew you'd love 'em.
I used to love jumping beans.
Totally forgot about 'em.
How did you know?
Well, knowing what people
secretly want is what I do.
Really?
What do I secretly want?
You sure you want me
to answer that?
Tell me.
Well, how about I do one better?
I'll just get you one.
It'll be my little gift to you.
One what?
Come in!
Commander, thank you very much.
What a great lunch suggestion.
It's delicious.
You want some?
No, no. I'm good. I just came to let
you know that this isn't a cartel hit.
How can you be sure?
The local police tell me that there's a field
very close, very secluded
where the Juarez cartel
put their bodies.
It's a custom.
Everybody around here
uses the field
when they
have a body to dump.
So not a local.
Could be an old client
with a beef
blames his lawyer
for prison time, wants payback.
Yeah. We need to look
at Firlock's case files.
I'll call Abbott.
Meet you back in Austin?
Yeah. I may be a little delayed.
I wanna go take another look
at the crime scene
before I roll outta here.
According to Firlock's colleagues
she had the best record
of any defense attorney
in the Fifth Circuit.
Gave the ASUAs hell
and did it with very little money.
No wonder
she was highly sought after.
But still, being a federal public defender
seems like a thankless job.
And they also said that threats
of violence from her clients
were very common.
These case files just arrived
from Fort Worth.
Fischer and Cho are on their way
to help you dig into 'em.
Looks like fun.
What exactly
are you looking for, Mr. Jane?
Well...
You didn't know
there was a body dump near here
but, you know,
that's to be expected.
You're an important state official.
But the locals knew.
And what better way is there to hide
your involvement in the crime
than to frame a cartel?
- There is no better way.
- Exactly.
So why dump the body here
and not in the body dump?
Must be because
it's more convenient here.
But why is it more convenient?
Mr. Jane.
Mr. Jane!
Mr. Jane?
What have you got, Wylie?
I searched border surveillance
for a 100-mile radius
around the city of Juarez.
And did Firlock's car pass through?
No. Her vehicle didn't clear
any bridges or border crossings
in the past 24 hours.
Okay. Well, if she was abducted,
she might've been in a different vehicle.
It's possible, but not likely.
Well, first of all, her car should've
been found abandoned by now.
We have half of Texas
looking for it.
Then there's the thermal-imaging
scanners at the border.
Even a body in a trunk will have
registered a heat signature
but there were no suspicious
reports last night.
All right. What about illegal routes?
I checked with the DEA
ICE, and border patrol...
No unusual sightings.
It... It... it's like Firlock appeared
in Juarez outta thin air.
- Hey, Jane.
- "I... I think I know how Edith"
"made it to Mexico but I need you
to track my phone."
Uh, just tell me where you are.
"Well, that's the problem.
I don't really know where I am."
Jane, I'm gonna need a little
more information than that.
Jane.
- What's wrong with Jane?
- I don't know.
Jane, are you there?
Well, these are the coordinates
Jane was calling from.
No, this can't be right.
We had to cross the border.
The map says
we're in Gentry, Texas, now.
We left Jane in Mexico.
Well, the Rio Grande's
right down there.
Let me try calling him again.
We got a truck coming
down the road.
What the hell you doing?
This is private property!
FBI, put down the rifle.
Show me your badge.
Can't do that until
you lower your weapon.
I ain't lowering my weapon
until you show me a badge.
"Uh, hey, guys."
"Sorry to interrupt. Um..."
"Just listen. Whatever happens...
whatever happens, don't shoot."
Ah!
Jane?
Jane, where did you come from?
Mexico!
In a tunnel!
"This is the Juarez cartel
we're talking about."
I had no choice
but to let them dig that tunnel!
You let them build
a thousand-yard tunnel into your land
and yet you got nothing
in return, Mr. Phelps?
Of course I did.
But what was I supposed to do?
They threatened my family.
We found blood on your land,
a lot of it...
200 feet
from your tunnel's entrance.
- I don't know anything about that.
- Type B, same as Edith Firlock.
- Who is Edith Firlock?
- The innocent woman you killed
and dragged through the tunnel
and dumped in Juarez.
It's only a matter of time
before we find your DNA on her body.
- That's not how it happened at all.
- No? Tell me.
Early yesterday morning,
I went to check on the cattle
saw some buzzards.
Drove out, thinking that
one of my herd was down.
Found that woman dead.
She was lying there with her arms
crossed, all creepy-like.
Last thing I needed
was cops snooping around.
So I moved her.
What'd you do with her car?
"There was no car.
It was just the body."
Mr. Phelps is guilty of many things
that will put him in jail for a long time.
But you don't think
he killed Firlock.
No, I don't.
Neither do I.
No?
We would've found more blood
in the tunnel.
So we agree.
I won't tell anyone if you don't.
But someone did kill that woman
on Phelps' property.
Someone who didn't know
about the tunnel
or they would've hidden
the body themselves.
What I'm more interested in
is how Phelps found the body.
With her arms crossed.
Well, it suggests a degree
of care.
So you think
the killer knew Firlock.
Oh, great.
Is this what I secretly want?
- Yeah, this better be good.
- Agent Fischer
I... I completed an image search
for that tattoo you sent over.
I'm sorry it took so long.
Firlock's tattoo is an insignia
for a legal defense fund
that closed down 25 years ago.
- She was a member?
- That's right.
They represented fringe groups, uh...
Oh, my God.
Is that a Tamagotchi?
Excuse me.
May I? Thank you.
I... I bought that for you.
I loved these things
so much as a kid!
I... I killed my fair share,
but I'm gonna keep this one alive.
- Thank you so much!
- My pleasure.
Wow. You must've been a real hoot
at other kids' birthday parties.
What was Firlock doing in Gentry?
It's a long way to drive for a day trip.
Mm. But it's a nice drive, though.
How you doing
on the case files?
They put me to sleep.
I decided to take a break
and look at her photo-share site.
Check this out.
These are the pictures she downloaded
the night before she left for Gentry.
- Farmers market. Lovely.
- I wonder where it is.
Well, that's easy...
Gentry.
- How do you know?
- Those wind turbines
are the same ones you can see
from Phelps' ranch.
Okay, so she sees
these photos on the internet
and the next day, she jumps in her car
for an all-day road trip?
Why does somebody do that?
Well, that corn on the cob
looks very tasty.
I could drive my Airstream
down to Gentry.
- Wanna join me?
- In the silver bucket? No, thanks.
Well, Fischer it is, then.
I'm still trying to track down
whoever tapped our cellphones
and killed Ardiles.
Van Pelt's got a lead
but I'm waiting for a judge
to sign off on a warrant
to search the property.
- Well, J.J. owes me a favor.
- Laroche?
Yeah, I heard he's working
Internal Affairs at SFPD.
You snap your fingers,
I bet he'll come running.
We're the last people he'd wanna help.
He lost his job because of us.
Well, I'm not saying
he's gonna wanna help us
but if you just mention
that I'm involved
and that, uh, you know,
he kind of owes me a favor
I think he'd be glad to help.
Just saying.
We're here already?
Yeah, well, we've been on the road
for five hours.
Oh. Guess I dozed.
All right.
Let's go meet the locals.
Here are some photos
of the victim we can show.
Well, it's lunchtime.
There's too many people.
Better to wait till the crowd
thins a bit.
- Where you going?
- I...
am going...
- to take a little nap.
- You're gonna sleep on the job?
Hi, there.
Hi. I was wondering
if you'd seen this woman
anywhere around here
in the past couple of days.
- We're trying to track her down.
- Who are you?
Kim Fischer.
I'm with the FBI.
Yeah, I don't know anything.
I will take that as a "no".
Thank you for your time.
I'll take one of those.
Our peanut butter
is all-natural and hand-ground.
Thank you.
Wow, that's really delicious.
- Clancy.
- Kim.
Clancy, you look like a man who knows
his way around this market.
Well, I've been working here
for a couple of years, so...
I could use your help.
Have you seen this woman?
She might've been here a few days ago
wearing a "Free Mandela" t-shirt.
Oh, yeah.
I remember the t-shirt.
I believe I gave her a sample.
Do you remember anything else?
Uh, did she have anyone with her?
So, are you the cop lady
everybody's talking about?
Cop lady?
Uh, I'm with the FBI.
As an officer of the law, you're required
to announce yourself.
Wow. Okay. Uh, an innocent woman
was murdered.
I'm just looking for information.
Oh, you want the truth, and yet
you approach me with artifice.
What's your name?
Special Agent Fischer.
- Special, indeed.
- Uh, well, Agent Fischer
how do you expect anyone to follow
the rules of the government
if you won't follow them yourself?
Hello, Laroche.
Looks like you're keeping busy.
As keen-eyed as ever,
young Rigsby.
Van Pelt.
Are you enjoying Internal Affairs?
Dealing with mistrust and disdain
for half the paycheck I got at CBI?
No, I am not enjoying
Internal Affairs.
But you're not here to discuss
my problems, are you?
I believe Lisbon called.
Your old team's phones
are being bugged, Ardiles' murder...
Yes, she...
she told me.
To be honest, I am not interested
in the headache
that seems to accompany you all.
As bad as this job is,
it's drama-free.
Good day.
Uh, we were told to remind you
that you owe Jane.
And if you help us out, your debt
with him will be settled.
I will... secure the warrant
and search the premises.
I will let you know
if I find anything.
I would like to assist
with the search.
You're no longer on active duty.
J.J., our lives are at risk here.
Drama... free.
Let's go.
Tough rodeo.
Tough, but not without rewards.
Clancy at the peanut butter stand
remembers giving Firlock a sample.
Oh. Well, that's interesting.
Yeah. Once he heard I was FBI
he shut down like everybody else.
Maybe someone found out Firlock
was a federal PD and took offense.
Well, that's a reasonable theory.
But it's wrong.
Where are you going?
Uh, well, you said that Edith
accepted a peanut butter sample?
Why would she do that?
Her medical alert bracelet
said that she was allergic to nuts.
Bingo. My turn.
Would you care to try some
freshly ground peanut butter?
Oh, yeah.
Don't mind if I do.
- That is delicious. You make that?
- Sure did.
Let me get a jar of that
for the road.
Thanks, and, um...
- And this, one of those. Thank you.
- Mm, how's 10 for both?
Very reasonable.
Where you headed?
Uh, probably west.
Yeah, no...
no set plan
just looking for some level road
to set the silver sovereign on.
- It's a nice rig.
- Yeah, it's home.
At least till I find someplace
to settle down.
Gonna get myself a farm
one day.
It's a good life.
"Gadsden Grove."
"Citizens farm."
- What's the deal with that, huh?
- Just homesteaders
focusing on living our own way.
Oh, yeah. Like...
like a commune?
Nah, none of that hippie stuff.
No, we're just steering clear
of the power grab going on out there.
I feel you.
If a man wants justice
and freedom in this world
he's gotta get it himself.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
Well, nice talking to you.
- Thank you. Better hit the road.
- Yeah.
Hey, you know, if, uh...
if it's farming you like,
you should come visit us.
Take a look-see.
- Well, I don't wanna be any trouble.
- No trouble.
Actually, I'm heading back there
right now.
Yeah, sure, why not?
That's a very generous offer.
- Patrick.
- Alex.
- It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
- You, too.
We got a report
on an abandoned vehicle
that matches the description
of Edith Firlock's car.
Really? Where is it?
"Ditched in a gully not far
from your current location."
Great. I'll drive over there with Jane
and we'll check it out.
Hey!
Hey, Jane! Jane!
"Yes, sir.
Sitting on 1,000 acres."
Plenty of space for crops, gardens
private living quarters.
- It's a sweet setup.
- Yep. It's home.
Fully licensed under
the state's concealed-carry laws.
Most of us on the farm here
choose to exercise
our second-amendment rights.
Well, if you like it, I love it.
How'd you end up here?
Well, like you, I looked
to the government for answers
after I got discharged...
only it didn't show up.
So I turned to the bottle
for support.
Well... I've been there.
Lucky for me, the farmer that owned
this place saw my struggle
and helped me
turn my life around.
When he died, he left me all this.
So I decided to do for others
what he did for me...
Help people
find a place to be free.
That's very impressive.
We're always open to good people.
Oh, I don't know.
Can't stay on the road forever, Patrick.
Gotta let it take you someplace.
Stay the night.
Think about it, huh?
Jane, where were you all night?
"I, um..."
I slept at the compound.
With the peanut-butter people?
"Yeah. They're really very nice."
Very nice. And...
and the air here is so clean.
I slept like a baby.
Are you ever coming back?
Yeah, well, as soon as I figure out
who killed Edith Firlock.
What makes you think
the killer's there?
"Well, she drove down to Gentry"
to get in touch with someone
from the peanut farm.
I mean, why else
would she dress like a rebel
and accept a food sample
that could possibly send her
into anaphylactic shock?
- Do you have any leads?
- No, but I have a plan.
"Daylight's a-burning, pilgrim."
Oh, uh, I'll be right out!
Um, I'm gonna need,
uh, a black helicopter and...
a tank.
Ha. Yeah, right.
I'm serious.
- What?
- I'm serious!
I know what we signed up for.
I... I know that we have to support him
and take a back seat to his whims
but he abandoned me
at the farmers market yesterday.
Okay, well, l... let's just think
about this for a second.
Jane is making
a sincere effort to fit in.
No, he's not.
Look at what he gave me
yesterday, huh?
- A robot.
- N-no, no, this is just not a robot.
This is Voltron, okay?
I used to love this when I was a kid.
Dennis... he ditched me.
Okay. Yeah.
Well, that's not cool.
No! No, that is far,
far from cool.
Okay, did Jane have something
to say about it afterwards?
Uh, who knows! He hasn't responded
to my texts or my phone calls ever since.
I... look,
where do we draw the line?
How far do we bend for this man?
I just got off the phone with Jane.
He says he needs a black helicopter,
a convoy of vans
and whatever you have
that looks most like a tank.
Uh, uh, Fischer...
What's her problem?
She'll be fine.
What in the hell
were you just talking about?
Pretty handy with that hammer.
Oh, I've used one
a time or two in my life.
Where'd you grow up?
What's wrong, Patrick?
That helicopter...
it's circling us.
- Must be some border issue.
- No. It's unmarked.
Dark-colored.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Somebody doesn't want us
to know who they are.
What was that about?
Well, I don't wanna freak anyone out
but this is usually how it starts.
They scope the property out
right before they, uh...
Before what?
That FBI agent yesterday,
the one Marcia got a picture of.
You know, she was trying to question us
about this missing woman.
- Feds must think we took her.
- Or killed her.
This will not do.
We're good people.
This is sovereign land.
Guys are a little paranoid,
aren't you?
It's not Waco.
It was one helicopter.
One black helicopter...
never a good sign...
- Unless, of course, you're lost.
- Yeah, better safe than sorry.
We should be preparing ourselves.
Prepare ourselves for what?
A black helicopter
was surveilling the property
not 10 minutes ago.
- A raid?
- Maybe.
Bobby, Katie, let's go!
"Come on, let's go!"
There's, like, a convoy of government
vehicles headed our way.
- How many?
- A lot.
- Oh, my God.
- I'll open the gun locker.
Whoa, now.
We need guns? Really?
It's just a helicopter, a few vans.
Easy, fellas.
Guys, does it have to be
so serious?
Can we just relax a little?
Guns down, people.
Go ahead. Guns down.
All right, everybody.
Lower your weapons.
That's better.
We came here to talk.
No gunplay, please.
My name's Alex Mildray.
I speak for Gadsden Grove.
Mr. Mildray, we have a warrant
to search these premises.
Search it for what?
Evidence pertaining to the abduction
and murder of Edith Firlock.
- Never heard of her.
- Well, that may be.
But somebody on this farm
has heard of her.
Look, we're coming in, sir
and I'd like to have your cooperation
before we do that.
You and I have the power
to save lives right now...
if we can work this out.
I speak for the farm,
but I don't decide.
We gotta put it to a vote.
Okay.
I give you an hour to persuade
your people to stand down.
Then we're coming in...
whether you voted for it or not.
"What do we wanna do, people?"
Do we wanna let
the feds in here?
No!
They say there's a murder suspect
among us.
How do we even know that's true?
We can't let the government
roll all over us.
Right!
They done that all our lives.
- Alex.
- Isn't that why we came here?
I like what you're doing here,
and I wanna help you.
Will you let me speak to them now?
I'm gonna say something
that may shock you
but if you work with me
I guarantee you will come out
of this a big hero.
You will be golden.
I promise.
Yes?
Yeah.
Okay, people.
Fellow citizens, my name is Patrick.
I'm not just a citizen
I'm also a sort of indentured servant
to the FBI out there.
- You're FBI?
- I'm with them, not of them.
Let him speak.
It's the truth.
There's a killer amongst you...
Murdered a good woman
by the name of Edith Firlock.
You know, I can find this
bloodthirsty killer right now
and I can take him out of here
and I can do it
without letting those accursed feds
cross your property line.
How does that sound?
Keep talking.
Edith Firlock drove down to Gentry
to, uh, catch up with someone
from her distant past...
A past where she was
a leftist lawyer.
So anyone under the age of 45
please go to the back
of the barn right now.
Under the age of 45...
back of the barn.
The rest of you, please...
Stay here.
Now, my guess
as to what happened here...
Edith Firlock knew a lot
of radical fringe types
from the old days.
One of those old friends...
is on the run
and using your farm to hide out.
Now, I think
Edith figured that out
and came down
to pay a visit.
Any takers?
The killer also owns their own gun.
Who here doesn't own a firearm?
To the back of the barn, please.
Now we're getting close.
The killer's starting
to get nervous.
The killer feels like
it's 110 degrees in here.
The killer's starting
to feel faint, it's so hot.
Which is not you or you.
Now we're getting very,
very close.
And I would suggest
that the killer can now see Edith...
every time they blink.
Yeah. You can see her, right?
Coming for revenge.
Right in the corner of your vision.
That poor woman.
Oh, stop it!
Marcia, right?
What's your real name, huh?
This is a lie!
Remember who he is!
He's a fed!
- He's the enemy!
- Marcia...
Marcia!
You don't wanna do this.
Don't tell me what I want!
I am so sick of you
telling everybody what they want
what to do, how to think!
Marcia...
it's over.
I ran your fingerprints and they tell
an interesting story, Marcia.
Or...
perhaps I should say...
Rachel.
In 1986, you were implicated
in an eco-terrorism bombing
just south
of the Canadian border.
You call it "terrorism".
We called it "liberating nature."
Edith Firlock's defense fund
represented you
until you skipped bail.
You know, 27 years
is a long time to be on the run.
Oh, it's not so bad
once you get past the first 10 years.
Until the past
shows up on your doorstep.
She said she saw my picture
on some travel blog
that she recognized me instantly.
"Rachel Solket..."
"I believe we need to talk."
"She told me
that if she found me"
"it was only a matter of time
before the authorities did."
"So Firlock showed up
to help you."
"Yeah...
help me turn myself in."
But you had no intention
of turning yourself in.
None whatsoever.
So you shot her at Phelps' ranch
and then you went back
to the market.
She should've left
well enough alone.
Yeah.
It was all her fault.
Hey, Laroche.
Do you have news?
I got the warrant.
I have a physical address
in Sacramento.
- Heading there now.
- That's great. Where is it?
Looks like
it's in the warehouse district.
Okay. Send me the address.
I'll join you.
Do you remember nothing
from our conversation?
Yeah, but I can help you.
I will search and let you know
if I find anything worth your time.
- Listen, Laroche, I...
- Goodbye, Rigsby.
- Hey, honey, you catch that?
- Yeah.
Looks like he's headed
towards Elk Grove.
I'll text you the address
once his car stops.
Thanks.
Uh, Wayne... be careful.
- I love you.
- "Love you."
Hi.
What do you want?
Oh, just wanted to apologize for leaving
you out there without a ride.
I understand.
- All in the line of duty.
- Yeah.
I got you that thing you wanted.
Oh, my God.
How did you...
Where'd you get that?
Jane gave it to me.
Jane gave you a wand?
When I was a girl
I thought I could change so many things
if I just had one of these.
Change what kinda things?
Oh, you know, uh,
make myself invisible
transport myself
to magical places.
You must've been disappointed
when it didn't work.
I never got one.
My mom thought all that princess stuff
was stupid nonsense.
She was right, of course.
Of course.
If you former CBI people
are one thing, it's predictable.
I can explain.
I need to search the premises alone.
You stay outside.
Police!
Search warrant!
"Rigsby!"
- Everything okay?
- No. It's not okay.
This place is creepy.
If you think I'm gonna search
this dump by myself
you are gravely mistaken.
Do you hear that?
Yeah. It sounded like
a man talking.
J.J.!
My... dog.
It's okay.
It's okay. Just...
Just stay with me.
Just s-stay...
stay with me.
It's okay.